<idea-plugin>
    <id>xyz.devglobe.plugin</id>
    <name>DevGlobe</name>
    <vendor email="contact@devglobe.xyz" url="https://devglobe.xyz">DevGlobe</vendor>

    <description><![CDATA[
    <p>Appear on a 3D globe in real time while you code. Your activity shows up live on <a href="https://devglobe.xyz">devglobe.xyz</a> — other developers can see you, discover your projects, and find your links.</p>

    <h3>How it works</h3>
    <ol>
        <li>Sign in on <a href="https://devglobe.xyz">devglobe.xyz</a> with GitHub</li>
        <li>Copy your API key from settings</li>
        <li>Open the DevGlobe tool window in your IDE and paste the key</li>
        <li>You appear on the globe</li>
    </ol>
    <p>The extension sends a heartbeat every 30 seconds while you code. It pauses automatically after 1 minute of inactivity. After 10 minutes without activity, you disappear from the globe.</p>

    <h3>Features</h3>
    <ul>
        <li><b>Live heartbeat</b> — your presence on the globe in real time</li>
        <li><b>Language detection</b> — uses your IDE's native FileType system, supports all languages</li>
        <li><b>Git integration</b> — detects your repo and tracks insertions/deletions over 24h</li>
        <li><b>Status message</b> — tell others what you're working on</li>
        <li><b>Repo sharing</b> — you decide whether your repo name is visible (off by default)</li>
        <li><b>Status bar</b> — your coding time today displayed live</li>
        <li><b>Notifications</b> — native IDE notifications for every action</li>
        <li><b>Offline recovery</b> — automatically resumes when the connection is back</li>
    </ul>

    <h3>What DevGlobe gives you</h3>
    <ul>
        <li><b>Visibility</b> — your GitHub, X, projects, and links accessible to all devs on the globe</li>
        <li><b>Network</b> — discover who's coding right now, in which language, and find their links</li>
        <li><b>Motivation</b> — weekly leaderboard by coding time + daily streak</li>
        <li><b>Project showcase</b> — highlight up to 10 projects on the globe</li>
    </ul>

    <h3>Privacy</h3>
    <p>This plugin is <a href="https://github.com/Nako0/devglobe-extension">open source</a>. Your source code, file contents, keystrokes, and IP address are <b>never sent</b>. Your location is approximate (~11 km). Your repo name is only visible if you explicitly enable it. Your API key is stored in your IDE's native credential manager (PasswordSafe).</p>

    <p>Compatible with all JetBrains IDEs: IntelliJ IDEA, WebStorm, PyCharm, GoLand, Rider, PhpStorm, CLion, RubyMine, DataGrip, Android Studio.</p>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <applicationService
            serviceImplementation="xyz.devglobe.plugin.settings.DevGlobeSettings"/>
        <applicationService
            serviceImplementation="xyz.devglobe.plugin.core.DevGlobeTracker"/>

        <toolWindow
            id="DevGlobe"
            anchor="right"
            icon="/icons/devglobe.svg"
            factoryClass="xyz.devglobe.plugin.ui.SidebarFactory"/>

        <statusBarWidgetFactory
            id="devglobe.statusBar"
            implementation="xyz.devglobe.plugin.ui.DevGlobeStatusBarFactory"
            order="after position"/>

        <postStartupActivity
            implementation="xyz.devglobe.plugin.DevGlobeStartupActivity"/>

        <notificationGroup id="DevGlobe"
            displayType="BALLOON"/>
    </extensions>
</idea-plugin>
